shouselaw.com 2017-07-27

# Privacy Policy | Shouse Law Group

Our law firm recognizes and respects your privacy. We want you to make the most of this Web site and to feel confident while doing so. The following discloses the information collection, use and disclosure practices for this domain. This policy does not address information obtained offline. 

Or you can reach us by telephone at the number posted on this page. 

## WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?

When you visit the public area of this website, you remain anonymous. To the extent you use forms, chats and e-mail links via the Web site, or call us via phone to communicate with us or anyone affiliated with us and provide us with personally identifiable information, however, you will not remain anonymous. Because it is impossible to predict every conceivable context in which such information might be provided to us via e-mail, we can provide you no assurance that personally identifiable information you choose to provide to us via e-mail will be maintained as private. 

This website uses "cookies." Cookies are small text files that are placed on a visitor's computer hard drive that allow us and/or the host of this Web site to record how many times a user or computers within a user's network of computers has visited the Web site, the number of times various pages of the Web site have been accessed and to track the user's home page customization preferences. You may disable receipt of cookies using features of your Web browser that disable or turn off cookies. We do not use cookies to retrieve information that is unrelated to your visit to or your interaction with this Web site. 

We collect your Internet Protocol (IP) address. An IP address is a number that is assigned to your computer when you use the Internet. The IP address data that we collect does not contain any personally identifiable information about you and is used to administer our site, to determine the numbers of different visitors to the site and to gather demographic data. However, when you submit information via this website, that information becomes identifiable and is kept on record as having come from your IP address. This information may be used to identify you on subsequent visits to this site, and to other sites associated with it, and to personalize your user experience. 

The non-personally identifiable data that this website collects is accessible by certain firm personnel as well as certain third-party Web site designers and personnel involved with the third-party service that hosts the Web site. We use all non-personally identifiable data that we collect internally and together with our Web site designer and host in order to improve the Web site. The information is used, for example, to evaluate what portions of the Web site are more popular than others, to determine where visitors to the site came from, and to determine how many times and how often particular pages of the site were accessed. We may use the data to prepare reports regarding Web site activity as part of the process of maintaining and improving the site. 

## WHAT STEPS DO WE TAKE TO PROTECT YOUR PRIVACY?

To the extent permitted by law, we will not sell, share, or otherwise disclose any of the information collected online without your express permission. 

## WHAT ARE THE PRIVACY POLICIES OF SITES TO WHICH THIS WEB SITE LINKS?

We provide links to third party Web sites that we do not control. Therefore, we urge you to review the privacy policies posted on these third party Web sites at the time you first visit such sites. We assume no obligation to review or ensure enforcement or compliance with the privacy policy of any Web site to which we links. 

## WHAT ABOUT CHILDREN'S PRIVACY?

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from any children under age 13. 

## IS DATA STORAGE AND PROCESSING CONDUCTED IN THE UNITED STATES?

Regardless of where you are located, the site collects information and processes and stores that information in databases located in the United States. 

## CAN WE REVISE THIS PRIVACY POLICY?

Due to the rapidly evolving technologies on the Internet, we may occasionally update this privacy policy. All revisions will be posted here Web site. We therefore urge you to review its Privacy Policy frequently. 

## WHAT IF I HAVE QUESTIONS ABOUT THIS PRIVACY POLICY?

Our Firm welcomes questions and comments this website and about this policy. You are welcome to call us with your comments and questions at the number listed on this page. 

## Renuncia

Nuestro bufete de abogados reconoce y respeta su privacidad. Queremos que aproveche al máximo este sitio Web y que se sienta seguro al hacerlo. A continuación se describen las prácticas de recolección, uso y divulgación de información para este dominio. Esta política no trata la información obtenida sin conexión.O puede comunicarse con nosotros por teléfono al número que aparece en esta página.  

¿QUÉ INFORMACIÓN PERSONAL RECOPILAMOS?Cuando usted visita el área pública de este sitio web, usted permanece anónimo. En la medida en que utilice formularios, chats y enlaces de correo electrónico a través del sitio Web, o llámenos por teléfono para comunicarse con nosotros o cualquier persona afiliada a nosotros y nos proporcionará información de identificación personal, sin embargo, no permanecerá anónimo. Debido a que es imposible predecir todos los contextos concebibles en los que tal información podría proporcionarnos a través del correo electrónico, no podemos ofrecerle ninguna garantía de que la información personal identificable que elija proporcionarnos por correo electrónico se mantendrá como privada.Este sitio web utiliza "cookies". Las cookies son pequeños archivos de texto que se colocan en el disco duro de un visitante, lo que nos permite a nosotros y / o al host de este sitio web registrar cuántas veces un usuario o computadoras de la red de computadoras de un usuario ha visitado el sitio web, Varias páginas del sitio Web se han accedido y para realizar un seguimiento de las preferencias de personalización de la página principal del usuario. Puede desactivar la recepción de cookies mediante las funciones de su navegador Web que deshabilitan o desactivan las cookies. No utilizamos cookies para recuperar información que no esté relacionada con su visita o con su interacción con este sitio web.Recopilamos su dirección de Protocolo de Internet (IP). Una dirección IP es un número asignado a su computadora cuando usa Internet. Los datos de dirección IP que recopilamos no contienen ninguna información de identificación personal sobre usted y se utilizan para administrar nuestro sitio, para determinar el número de visitantes diferentes del sitio y para recopilar datos demográficos. Sin embargo, cuando usted envía información a través de este sitio web, esa información se identifica y se mantiene en el registro como proveniente de su dirección IP. Esta información se puede utilizar para identificarlo en visitas posteriores a este sitio, ya otros sitios asociados con él, y para personalizar su experiencia de usuario.Los datos que no son de identificación personal que recopila este sitio son accesibles para ciertos empleados de la empresa, así como para ciertos diseñadores y personal de sitios web de terceros involucrados con el servicio de terceros que aloja el sitio Web. Utilizamos todos los datos no identificables que recopilamos internamente y junto con nuestro diseñador y anfitrión del sitio Web para mejorar el sitio Web. La información se utiliza, por ejemplo, para evaluar qué partes del sitio Web son más populares que otras, para determinar de dónde proceden los visitantes del sitio y para determinar cuántas veces y con qué frecuencia se accedieron a determinadas páginas del sitio. Podemos utilizar los datos para preparar informes sobre la actividad del sitio Web como parte del proceso de mantenimiento y mejora del sitio.  

¿QUÉ PASOS TOMAMOS PARA PROTEGER SU PRIVACIDAD?En la medida permitida por la ley, no venderemos, compartiremos ni divulgaremos de ninguna otra forma la información recopilada en línea sin su permiso expreso.  

¿CUÁLES SON LAS POLÍTICAS DE PRIVACIDAD DE LOS SITIOS A LOS QUE SE ENLACE ESTE SITIO WEB?Proporcionamos enlaces a sitios web de terceros que no controlamos. Por lo tanto, le recomendamos que revise las políticas de privacidad publicadas en estos sitios web de terceros en el momento en que visita por primera vez dichos sitios. No asumimos ninguna obligación de revisar o garantizar la aplicación o el cumplimiento de la política de privacidad de cualquier sitio Web al que nos vinculamos.  

¿QUÉ ACERCA DE LA PRIVACIDAD DE LOS NIÑOS?No recopilamos a sabiendas información de identificación personal de niños menores de 13 años.  

¿SE REALIZA EL ALMACENAMIENTO Y EL PROCESAMIENTO DE DATOS EN LOS ESTADOS UNIDOS?Independientemente de dónde se encuentre, el sitio recopila información y procesos y almacena esa información en bases de datos ubicadas en los Estados Unidos.  

¿PODEMOS REVISAR ESTA POLÍTICA DE PRIVACIDAD?Debido a la rápida evolución de las tecnologías en Internet, ocasionalmente podemos actualizar esta política de privacidad. Todas las revisiones se publicarán aquí en el sitio Web. Por lo tanto, le recomendamos que revise su Política de privacidad con frecuencia.

¿QUÉ PASA SI TENGO PREGUNTAS SOBRE ESTA POLÍTICA DE PRIVACIDAD?Nuestra Firma agradece las preguntas y comentarios de este sitio web y de esta política. Le invitamos a que nos llame con sus comentarios y preguntas al número que aparece en esta página.
